[{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Throughput?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Error_Rate?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Jitter?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Latency?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Interplay_Factors?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Bandwidth?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"bw","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Congession?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"None Of The Above","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Computer_Networks?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"p3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"perfo","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"p2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"n1","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Security?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"availabilty","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"modi","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"confid","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"integ","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"interrr","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"sec","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},{"questionBody":"Which of the following definitions describes the concept Scope?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"s1","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s2","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s3","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"s4","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"scope","isCorrectAnswer":true}],"strategy":"Class"},null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"NCP is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard is a subClass from Session","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Media_Access_Control_Sublayer is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Presentation is a subClass from Data_Link","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Extranet is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Protocol is a subClass from Scope","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Application_Layer is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Topology is a subClass from IP_Suite","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Firewall is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Fabrication is a subClass from System_Security","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Spammer_Programs is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Passive_Attacks is a subClass from Malicious_Software","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,{"questionBody":"Which of the following sentences true?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Active_Hub is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Modem is a subClass from Hub","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Routing_table is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Repeater is a subClass from Router","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"Termenology"},null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,null,{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Application\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"Network\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"ISO_Standard\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"Data_Link\tuses\tRADIUS","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"},{"questionBody":"Which one of the following response pairs are related ?","choices":[{"id":0,"text":"Internet_Society\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":true},{"id":0,"text":"eMail\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"VOIP\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false},{"id":0,"text":"RFC\tcommittee\tIAB","isCorrectAnswer":false}],"strategy":"property"}]